Dmitrii Lisin

Software Programmer, Embedded Programmer

190000, Saint Petersburg, Saint Petersburg RU

@mrlisdim (https://t.me/mrlisdim)

in dmitrii-lisin (https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmitrii-lisin/)



Linux | Reading schematics |

Datasheet exploring

Since childhood, I'm in love with programming. Started my carer as an intern in an electronics design company, I found out that I love to create something that works in real life, not just inside my computer. Have finished a lot of embedded projects from different spheres and had deal with a numerous of instruments, protocols and peripherals. Has always been intended to write only high quality and human-readable code. Had an experience as a team leader, but prefer to work as an equal part of team.

SKILLS

Embedded Development Master	Python Development Advanced	CI/CD Intermediate
C/C++ Zephyr FreeRTOS STM32 Nordic Real-time protocols Industrial protocols Stack only programming	FastAPI Pydantic ORM WAMP protocol Async Threading	Docker Docker Compose Github Actions Gitlab Pipelines
Web Development Intermediate	Rust Beginner	Common VSC Gitlab Github Reviewing

WORK EXPERIENCE

React | Parcel | Rollup

2020 - Current

Team leader at LLC "Third Pin"

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Typescript |

Developed a flexible testing system for embedded electronics based on distributed micro-services connected by PubSub/RPC Web-protocol.

- Robster: flexible testing system for electronic devices (Python, WAMP, Microservice, Docker, PostgreSQL)
- Gate valve controller (ARM, STM32, Zephyr, Modbus)
- GPS tracker for a professional training (ARM, Nordic, GPS, UBlox, Ant)

Tauri

2013 - 2020

Embedded Software Developer at LLC "Third Pin"

Have been finished more than 20 commercial projects in embedded area including IoT, safety systems, shipbuilding.

- Pastilda: hardware password manager (STM32, ARM, Crypto Peripheral, SDIO, FatFS, FreeRTOS)
- Ship ruder control system (ARM, STM32, USB HID, FreeRTOS)
- Fire alarm system (ARM, STM32)
- MTUTA: Telemetry of vending machines (ARM, FreeRTOS, USB, SD, SIMCom, GSM, Ethernet, FTP)

PROJECTS

Pastilda

2016 - 2017

team/pastilda) https://bitbucket.org/thirdpin_team/pastilda (https://bitbucket.org/thirdpin_team/pastilda)

Skills acquired: C++ | Embedded | Open-source

Open-source hardware designed to manage our credentials in handy and secure way.

Just Run My Debugger!

2021 - Current

Ithtps://github.com/ila-embsys/justrunmydebugger (https://github.com/ila-embsys/justrunmydebugger)

Skills acquired: Rust | Rescript | Tauri | React

Pet project, simple GUI for OpenOCD debugger.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Intelligent Technologies in Robotics at ITMO University 2012 - 2016

LANGUAGES

English Russian
Fluent Native Speaker

INTERESTS

Games Books Traveling

Hobby programming

REFERENCES

""

Ivan Larionov, LLC "Third Pin" CEO